Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Affiliated Units
    - Yale Cancer Center Conflict of Interest, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Yale Cancer Center National Cancer Institute Site Visit, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Center for Biomedical and International Technology, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Center for the Study of American Art and Material Culture Director Appointment Cooke, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence Botin Foundation Collaboration Report, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence Department of Defense and Yale Technical Exchange, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence Floor Plan, c. 2013 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence Per Lab Annual Report, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence Summary and Notes, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence Symposium, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Center for Interntional and Professional Experience Annual Report, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Center for Interntional and Professional Experience Survey Report, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Affliliated Units Center for International and Area Experience Annual Report, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Center for Research on Race Indigeneity and Global Cultures at Yale, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Yale Center for the Study of Globalization Zedillo Notes, 2013 April 9 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Center for Teaching and Learning Mission and Vision, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Child Study Center Comer Notes, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Child Study Center Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Climate and Energy Institute Advisory Board Overview, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Climate and Energy Institute Climate Projections Program, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Climate and Energy Institute Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Climate and Energy Institute Pachauri, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Climate and Energy Institute Perspectives, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Climate and Energy Institute Patchy Notes, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Climate and Energy Institute Summary Report, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Coalition for Mental Health and Well Being at Yale Correspondence, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Communication Center Presidential Media Techniques, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Gilder Lehrman Center notes, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Gilder Lehrman Center Report, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Gilder Lehrman Center Report and Overview, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Institute for Biospheric Studies Director Announcement Schmitz, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Dwight Hall at Yale Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Economic Growth Center Director Appointment Rosenzweig, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Yale Entrepreneurial Institute, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Entrepreneurship Institute, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Evan Hall Opening Conference, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Global Health Leadership Institute-Summary, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Greenberg Conference Center Reception, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies Chair Interview, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies Disc, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies Director Appointment Schmitz, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Yale Institute for Network Science Article, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Institute for the Preservation of Cultural Hearitage Memorandum of Understanding, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Institute of Sacred Music Annual Report, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Institute of Sacred Music Annual Report, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Institute of Sacred Music Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Institute of Sacred Music Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Institute of Sacred Music Director Reappointment Jean, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Institute of Sacred Music Notes, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies Chair Interviews, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies Director Appointment Hacker, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies Hacker Meeting Notes 28 March, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Jackson Institute Annual Council Meeting, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Jackson Institute Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Jackson Institute Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Jackson Institute Levinsohn International Affairs Consolidation, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Jackson Institute Mohan Notes 2014 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Jackson Institute Negroponte Correspondence, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Johnson Center Kissinger Papers Advisory Board, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Koerner Center, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - MacMillan Center African Initiative Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - MacMillan Center Annual Report, 2012-2014 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - MacMillan Center Deputy Director Appointment Announcement, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - MacMillan Center Director Appointment Shapiro, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - MacMillan Center Notes, c.2013 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - MacMillan Center Shapiro, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Marsh Botanical Garden Director Appointments, 2008-2014 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - McDougal Center Donor and Director Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Jack Miller Center Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Quantum Institute Proposal, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Yale Reperatory Theatre Ephemera, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Yale Rudd Center for Food Policy and Obesity Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Saint Thomas More Chapel Events, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Yale Science and Engineering Society Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Slifka Center Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Yale Stem Cell Center Whitepaper, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Tantaquidgeon Institute for Indigenous and Diasporic Inquiry Proposal, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Whitney Humanities Center Annual Report, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Whitney Humanities Center Annual Report, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine Budget and Financial Plan, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine Financial Plan, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine Meeting, 2013 November 14 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine Proposal, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine Vice President's Meeting, 2014 August 28 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Yale Center Beijing, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Yale Center Beijing Conference, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Yale Daily Herald Luncheon, 2014 February 14 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Yale Health Pharmacy Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital Borgstrom, 2014 July 8 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Yale Review Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Yale-China Association Meeting, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Yale-China Leadership Center Dinner Notes, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute Correspondence, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute Fry and Vivian meeting, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute National Initiative, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute Notes, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute University Advisory Council Meeting, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Art Galleries, Libraries and Museums
    - Complaints, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Yale University Art Gallery Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Yale University Art Gallery Director Reynolds Extension, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Yale University Art Gallery Director Reynolds Review, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Yale University Art Gallery Governing Board, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Yale University Art Gallery Koster and Koerner, 2014 November 5 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Yale University Art Gallery Reynolds Meeting Notes, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Beinecke Correspondence, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Center for British Art Annual Report, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Center for British Art Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Center for British Art Paul Mellon Centre Board of Governors Meeting, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Center for British Art Paul Mellon Centre Board of Governors Meeting, 2014 February 10 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Center for British Art Meyers Notes, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Harvey Cushing and John Hay Whitney Medical Library Annual Report, 2013-2015 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Fortunoff Video Archive, 2012-2014 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Benjamin Franklin Papers Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Robert Haas Arts Library Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Manuscripts and Archives Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Manuscripts and Archives Correspondence, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Peabody Museum Board of Curators, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Peabody Museum Budget Meetings, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Peaboy Museum Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Peaboy Museum Director, 2007-2014 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Peabody Museum Director Appointment Skelly, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Peabody Museum Director Briggs Appointment, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Peabody Museum Director Briggs Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Peabody Museum Director Search, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Sterling Library Restoration Announcements, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Yale University Library Goals and Priorities, 2012-2014 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Yale University Library Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Yale University Library Publishers Presentation, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Athletics
    - General Files, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - General Files, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Presentation, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Athletically-Related Income, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Athletics and Yale Preservation, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Blue Leadership Ball, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Complaints, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Field Hockey Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Football Class of 2018 Team, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Football Competition, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Football Concussion Summary, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Football Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Football Harvard and Yale Brunch, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Funds Generated at Yale, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Golf and Tennis Salovey Swensen Extravaganza Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Men's Ice Hockey Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - National Collegiate Association Compliance, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - National Collegiate Association Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - National Collegiate Association Violation Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Pool, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Pool Renovation, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Requests, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Softball Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Squash Facilities Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Yale Swimming, Diving and Water Polo Alumni Group Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Tennis, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Tennis, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Tennis Check Logs, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Tennis Connecticut Open Announcements, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Tennis Extravaganza, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Tennis Levin Swensen Talking Points, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Yale Bowl "Hero's Day at Yale Bowl", 2013 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Yale Bowl Publication, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Yale vs Harvard Brunch, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Yale Sports Federation Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Yale Sports Federation Meeting, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Awards
    - ACE Fellowship Report, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Award for Diversity and Inclusion Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Blavatnik Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Breakthrough Prize in Life Sciences Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Ron Brown Scholars Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Circle of Excellence Award Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Congratulations, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Wilbur Cross Medal Award Celebrations, 2013 October 15 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Wilbur Cross Medal Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Wilbur Cross Medal Dinner, 2013 October 15 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Wilbur Cross Medal Reception, 2014 October 14 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Davis United College Scholars Program Publication, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Emmy Award Modern Family Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Department of Energy Computational Science Graduate Fellowship Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Durham International Fellowship for Research and Enterprise Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Albert Einstein World Award of Science and Leonardo da Vinci World Award of Art Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Dwight D Eisenhower Global Leadership Award Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Emerging leaders in Academic Medicine Fellowship Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Fox International Fellows Luncheon, 2013 September 16 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Fulbright Program Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Fulbright Nehru Lecturing Fellowship Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Genesis Prize Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - German Academic Exchange Service (DAAD) Scholarships Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Gruber Cosmology Prize Dinner, 2014 October 1 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Guggenheim Fellowships Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Charles Homer Haskins Prize Lecture, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Heineken Prizes Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Ho-Am Prize Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Holberg International Memorial Prize Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Howland Memorial Prize Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Institute Honor Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - International Boundless Scholarship Program Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - International Prize for Biology Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Kavli Prize Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Kentucky Colonel Salovey Certificate, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Kluge Prize Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Kwok Scholarship Program Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Kravis Prize Gus Speth Nomination, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Aldo Leopold Award Dinner, 2014 November 10 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Richard U Light Fellowship Program Annual Report, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Richard U Light Fellowship Program Annual Report, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Luminary Award Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Marshall Scholars Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Harold W McGraw Jr. Prize in Education, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Napier Banquet Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - National Humanities Center Fellow Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - National Humanities Medal Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Nobel Prize Rothman Press Conference, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - President's for Staff Excellence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - President's Public Service Fellows List, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Raymond and Beverly Sackler International Prize in Biophysics Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Hanns Martin Schleyer-Stiftung Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Paul and Daisy Soros Fellowhips for New Americans Visit, 2014 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Sterling Fellows, 2014 May 1 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Tang Prize Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Tony Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Visionary Leadership Award Maya Lin Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Volvo Entertainment Prize Correspondence, 2104 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Branco Weiss Fellowship Correspondence, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Robert A Welch Award in Chemistry Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Donald Windham Sandy M. Campbell Literature Prizes Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Donald Windham Sandy M. Campbell Literature Prizes Ceremony, 2013 September 10 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Boards
    - Connecticut Council for Education Reform, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Connecticut Council for Education Reform Accountability Plan for Bridgeport Public Schools, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Connecticut Council for Education Reform Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Connecticut Coundil for Education Reform Correspondence, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Connecticut Council for Education Reform Meeting, 2014 December 8 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Connecticut Council for Education Reform Overview and Correspondence, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Connecticut Council for Education Reform Simons Report, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Federation of Associations in Behavioral and Brain Sciences (folder 1 of 2), 2011-2014 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Federation of Associations in Behavioral and Brain Sciences (folder 2 of 2), 2011-2014 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Federation of Associations in Behavioral and Brain Sciences Conference Call, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Foundation for Bluegrass, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Gruber Foundation Meeting, 2013 December 7 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Gruber Foundation Meeting, 2014 December 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Gruber Foundation Meeting, 2014 May 5 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - International Bluegrass Museum Hager Charitable Trust Agreement, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - National Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - National Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse Proposal, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - New Haven Promise (folder 1 of 3), 2013 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - New Haven Promise (folder 2 of 3), 2013 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - New Haven Promise (folder 3 of 3), 2013 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - New Haven Promise, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - New Haven Promise, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - New Haven Promise Analysis of Progress Report, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - New Haven Promise Annual Scholar Celebration, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - New Haven Promise Brochures, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - New Haven Promise Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - New Haven Promise FERPA Waiver, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - New Haven Promise Ginsberg Notes, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - New Haven Promise Grievances, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - New Haven Promise Meeting, 2013 October 1 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - New Haven Promise Meeting, 2013 December 17 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - New Haven Promise Meeting, 2014 March 3 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - New Haven Promise Meeting, 2014 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - New Haven Promise Meeting (folder I of 2), 2014 September 29 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - New Haven Promise Meeting (folder 2 of 2), 2014 September 29 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - New Haven Promise Transforming an Urban School System, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Sheffield Scientific School Annual Board Meeting, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Sheffield Scientific School Annual Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Yale New Haven Health Annual Report, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Yale New Haven Health Assessment, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Yale New Haven Health Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Yale New Haven Health System Report and Plan, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital Meeting and Credit Approval, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital and Yale New Haven Health System (folder 1 of 2), 2013 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital and Yale New Haven Health System (folder 2of 2), 2013 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital and Yale New Haven Health System Borgstrom Background, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital and Yale New Haven Health System Leadership Attributes, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Yale University Press Director Donatich Announcement, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Yale University Press Meeting (folder 1 of 2), 2013 October 18 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Yale University Press Meeting (folder 2 of 2), 2013 October 18 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Yale University Press Meeting, 2013 November 8 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Yale University Press Meeting, 2014 October 6 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Yale University Press Meetings, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Yale University Press London Articles of Association, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Yale University Press London Governing Documents, 2014-2015 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Yale University Press London Meeting, 2014 May 9 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Yale University Press London Trustees Invitations, 2014-2015 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Chronological Files
    - Part I, 2013 July 1-2013 July 5 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Part II Blue List, 2013 July 5 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Part III, 2013 July 8-2013 July13 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Part IV Blue List, 2013 July 2-2013 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Part V, 2013 July 12-2013 July 19 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Part VI Blue List, 2013 July 3-2013 July 19 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Part VII, 2013 July 22-2013 July 26 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Part I, 2013 August 2 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Part II, 2013 August 1-2013 August 9 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Part III Blue List, 2013 August 6-2013 August 9 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Part IV (folder 1 of 2), 2013 August 14-2013 August 16 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Part IV (folder 2 of 2), 2013 August 14-2013 August 16 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Part V, 2013 August 20-2013 August 23 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Part VI, 2013 August 26-2013 August 30 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Part I (folder 1 of 2), 2013 September 6 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Part 1 (folder 2 of 2), 2013 September 6 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Part II, 2013 September 10-2013 September 13 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Part III Blue List 10 and 10A, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Part IV, 2013 September 17-2013 September 20 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Part V, 2013 September 20 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Part VI, 2013 September 26-2013 September 30 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Part I, 2013 October 1-2013 October 4 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Part II, 2013 October 7-2013 October 11 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Part III, 2013 October 11-2013 October 17 (Box 13, Folder 12)